[Music] Of
[Música]
course now the
claro ahora se van a entregar los
resources are going to be delivered now they have delivered it
recursos ahora han entregado entregó los
Pina's lawyers delivered one in
abogados de pinas entregaron uno
November which is the one that has answered the
noviembre que es el que ha contestado la
accusation now and they have also delivered
acusación ahora y además han entregado
another one that now that other one
ellos otro que ahora ese otro Tienen que
The lawyers Pin and the prosecutor have to answer I mean
contestar los abogados Pin y el fiscal O
or I mean now because of
sea quiero decir o sea ahora porque
course this resource I have seen as if it
claro este recurso yo he visto como que
were part of appealing their issues it is
fuera parte de apelar sus cuestiones es
like it responds to some issues
como que responde a algunas cuestiones
not those presented by the part of
no de las que presenta el la parte de
Ewin let's say now what is the next
ewin digamos ahora cuál es el siguiente
step we have two parts or we have what we
paso tenemos dos partes oa tenemos lo
have is the response
que nosotros tenemos es la contestación
to Ospina's appeal or that is
del recurso de ospina o sea ello es lo
what not what they presented on March 16th was the response to Pina's appeal Well I say Pina but not Pina
Pina Bueno yo digo Pina pero no Pina en
actually it is the lawyers of the R
realidad es los abogad de la familia r
entos family par opina so that people do not I do not
entos par opina para que la gente no no
know So what they have presented is that is
se Entonces ellos lo que han presentado
a response but apart from the
eso es una contestación pero aparte del
26th they presented another is another
26 ellos presentaron otro es otro
appeal and now that appeal
recurso de apelación y ahora ese recurso
when it reaches the parties when it
cuando le llegue a las partes cuando
reaches the part of the Pin and all the
llegue a la parte de los pin y todo el
roll they will have to read it study it and they
rollo tendrán que leerlo estudiarlo y
will have a deadline to  answer it clearly
tendrán un plazo para contestarlo claro
they can go asking for postponements
ellos pueden ir pidiendo aplazamientos
like these people have done since
como han hecho esta gente desde
November with the do pino That is, December
noviembre con el do pino O sea Diciembre
January
enero febrero y marzo 4atro meses para
February and March 4 other months to answer the two pinas now you want to browse the internet safely and also access all the content of your favorite platforms like Netflix HBO Max or Disney Plus cyberghost VPN And I don't know if you know but there is content that is not available in your country
contenidos que en tu país no están
and with this trick you can
disponibles y con este truquillo puedes
access all the content wherever you
acceder a todo el contenido estés donde
are I don't know if you know what a VPN is
estés no sé si sabes lo que es una VPN
but it is an extension that you put on your
pero es una extensión que le pones a tu
internet with which you mask the IP and
internet con la que en mascaras la IP y
apart from browsing completely safely and
aparte de Navegar completamente seguro y
anonymously without anyone being able to know who you
anónimo sin que nadie pueda saber quién
are and where you are It helps you access
eres y dónde estás Te sirve para acceder
some content that is
a algunos contenidos que están
blocked in your country there are movies and
bloqueados en tu país hay películas y
series on your favorite platforms that
series en tus plataformas favoritas que
are not available there are
no están disponibles hay programas de
television programs for example on mediaset
televisión por ejemplo en mediaset
content that if you try to watch them outside
contenidos que si los intentas ver fuera
of Spain they have a geoblock that does not
de España tienen un geobloqueo que no te
allow you Well with Cyber ​​Ghost VPN that is
lo permite Pues con Cyber Ghost VPN eso
over apart from being protected
se acabó aparte de estar protegido
browsing anonymously you will be able to
navegando bajo el anonimato podrás
access content from all over the
acceder a los contenidos de todo el
planet and you will also have Total privacy
planeta además tendrás privacidad Total
since it keeps your connection private and
ya que mantiene tu conexión en privado y
protects your data Ultra fast speed
protege tus datos velocidad Ultra rápida
to eliminate the lake in any
para eliminar el lago en cualquier juego
online game with which you can enjoy
online con los que podrás disfrutar de
live broadcasts without interruptions and as I have already
directos sin interrupciones y como ya os
told you Freedom to access all the
he dicho Libertad para acceder a todo el
content on the planet wherever and whenever
contenido del planeta dónde y cuando
you want also take advantage of the 2%
quieras además aprovecha T 2% de
discount using the link that I
descuento utilizando el enlace que te
leave you in the description of this video and be careful
dejo en la descripción de este vídeo y
because you can try Cyber ​​Ghost VPN
ojo porque puedes probar Cyber Ghost VPN
45 days without obligation and if you are not
45 días sin compromiso y si no te
convinced, ask for a refund and they will return
convence pides el reembolso y te
the pza So do not wait any longer
devuelven la pza Así que no esperes más
to protect your connection and increase your
para proteger tu conexión y aumentar tu
internet experience, run click on the
experiencia en internet corre click al
link in the description and take advantage of
enlace de la descripción y aprovecha
this super offer cyberghost VPN to
esta superoferta cyberghost VPN para
browse completely free and secure
navegar completamente libre y seguro
we continue with the video lar and metap
seguimos con el vídeo lar y metap se
have to study Daniel Sancho's appeal
tienen que estudiar el recurso de Daniel
And if now they stick together for four months
Sancho Y si ahora se pegan cuatro meses
just like they have stuck together we are in
igual que se han pegado ellos estamos en
March because now they can do the
marzo porque ahora ellos pueden hacer lo
same thing the same strategy say now well
mismo la misma estrategia decir ya pues
now we are going to ask for resources let's
ahora vamos ir pidiendo recursos vamos
ask or so it goes man, I mean now
pidiendo o sea así va tío o sea ahora
the others also have to respond to
tienen que responder los otros también a
this and when and when the court
esto y cuando y cuando el tribunal se
gets to but if I were me if I were
pone a pero que yo si fuera yo si fuera
the lawyer Pina now I am going to ask for a
el abogado Pina ahora va pid
summons  until I we just like they have done
emplazamiento hasta que me we igual que
they collect now in March
han hecho ellos recogen ahora en marzo
Well then April May June June Maybe
Bueno pues abril mayo junio junio A lo
when I answer when I answer
mejor cuando conteste cuando conteste
this it will be November but when the when the
esto es noviembre pero cuando el cuando
ewin part answers this to this
la parte de ewin conteste a este a est
now is when the judges study them
ahora es cuando los jueces los estudian
and they will resolve it and at that moment it
y y van a resolverlo y en ese momento
could take from one to two years until they
puede pasar de uno a 2 años hasta que
answer that appeal my goodness and then
contesten a ese recurs madre mía y luego
when they answer that appeal whatever
cuando contesten a ese recurso salga lo
comes out it will be fought again if it is
que salga se va a volver a pelar si sale
favorable which I doubt it is for Daniel Sancho the
favorable que lo dudo a Daniel Sancho la
Rieta family will fight and if it is
familia rieta va a pelar y si sale
favorable to the Rieta family the Sanchos will fight and
favorable a la familia rieta los sanchos
we will do the same
van a pelar y volvemos a hacer el mismo
process again for the Supreme Court How
proceso para el tribunal supremo Qué
different different different is not that they are
diferente difente diferente no es que se
going to spend 8 years fighting that This
van a pegar los 8 años pelando qu Este
good step let's see but with the sentence he
paso bueno a ver pero con la condena que
has and even if he is lucky that
tiene y incluso teniendo suerte que
something beneficial comes out of here for
saliera algo beneficioso de aquí para
Daniel Sancho he would not even reach uh
Daniel Sancho incluso no llegaría a eh
exceed the terms of what
superar los plazos de de lo que fuera
a sentence would be because with a lot of luck the
una condena porque con mucha suerte lo
best that could happen to him would be for them to
mejor que le podía pasar que fuera que
reduce his years no then sorry
le redujeran los años no entonces perón
but they will never  never be less F if we're going
pero nunca van a ser nunca menos F si
on in years When you realize no, we have
vamos echando años Cuando te des cuenta
n't been there for 8 years and the 8 years
no no hemos pegado 8 años y los 8 años
were fighting, that is, different Now I'm appealing
pelando o sea diferente Ahora recurro
Okay, now these people have answered the
Vale ahora ha contestado esta gente al
deina appeal, that's what I resolved, remember
recurso deina ese lo resol acuérdate de
the appeals in Yuji's case,
los recursos de la la del caso de yuji
in Frank's case, Yuji spent 6 years
de lo de Frank que yuji estuvo 6 años
fighting to appeal until he got
peleando recurrir hasta que hasta que
out. This is going to be 6 years, at 6 years
salió pu Esto va ser 6 años a los 6 años
they can already start the process of coming to
ya pueden iniciar el proceso de venir a
Spain. But of course, there has to
España Pero claro con una salvedad tiene
be a final sentence if you get caught in
que tener condena firme si te pilla
the middle of an appeal, not at six, no, er, I don't think so,
medio un recurso no a los seis no er cre
not at 6 they can start the process
no a los 6 pueden empezar el trámite
then I'll have to, but I think they
luego te haar pero pero yo creo que el
can start the process even at
trámite lo pueden empezar incluso a los
4, but one thing is to start the
4 pero una cosa es que empieces el
process and another very different thing is that I grant it to you, it
trámite y otra muy diferente que te lo
takes a while, but apart from that,
concedo tarda un tiempo pero aparte
when you've already asked for the Royal Pardon, you already
cuando ya hayas pedido el Perdón Real ya
have the final sentence, which it doesn't
tengas las sentencia en firme que no la
have, so what does that mean? If
tiene o sea eso qué quiere decir si yo
now I spend 6 years appealing, I've been 6
ahora me pego 6 años apelando yo estoy 6
years without a final sentence without being able to
años sin condenar en firme sin poder
do anything, you can't  do nothing you
hacer nada no puedes hacer nada tú no
can't p request anything you can't do not
puedes p solicitar nada no puedes hacer
even this Royal Pardon or ask for
ni siquiera el Perdón Real este ni pedir
the reductions Because right now but
las reducciones Porque ahora mismo pero
you think that we stick 6 years fighting
tú pes que nos pegamos 6 años a pelando
and I already have the option to ask to be
y yo tengo ya la opción de pedir que
able to come to Spain in 2 years
pueda venir a España dentro de 2s años
for example that says well for the 4
por ejemplo que dice bueno para los 4
years you can request it you can't because
años puedes solicitarlo no puede porque
to request it you have to have
para solicitarlo tienes que tener
firm convictions Jose when the
condenas firme José cuando terminen los
appeals end we won't recognize you Eh well now it
recursos no te reconocemos Eh bueno ya
's different from when we
so diferente a cuando
started Give me, do you see a minimum
empezamos Dame le ves un mínimo de
possibility that something will come out
posibilidad a que salga algo
evidently I'm talking about a solution
evidentemente estoy hablando un solución
but something beneficial for Daniel Sancho
pero algo beneficioso para Daniel Sancho
a minimum something to what they say Well I don't
una mínima algo a lo que digan Bueno no
know what I know, I think that in Spain
sé yo que sé yo creo que en España
when now we are going to go over
cuando ahora vamos a ir repasando
some things but Jos I think that here
algunas cosas pero Jos yo creo que aquí
in Spain There are things about this appeal that would
en España Hay cosas de este recurso que
come out well from the appeal no because
le saldrían bien del recurso no porque
the appeal is not based on any evidence
el recurso no se basa en ninguna prueba
the appeal is based solely on
el recurso se basa únicamente en la
Daniel's word Yes
palabra de Daniel Sí
but issues and that are the ones with which they
pero cuestiones e que son las de la con
request the annulment has one
las que solicitan la anulación tiene una
that they have presented that the documentary from
que han presentado que el documental de
HBO and from and from Skit Time Do you think that
de hbo y de y de skit Time Tú crees que
a judge here in Spain for  an
un juez aquí en España por un documental
hbo or skich Time documentary would annul a trial
de hbo o skich Time anularía un juicio
eh sincerely Look Marta, how is the castle
eh sinceramente Mira Marta el castillo
and it has bigger things
cómo está y tiene cosas de peso más
than an hbo documentary and so on I'm
grandes que un documental de hbo y demás
talking to you about Spain eh I'm talking to you about Spain
te hablo de España eh Te hablo de España
with Spain with that resource they clean their
con España con ese recurso limpian el
ass but the question of the document
culo pero la cuestión de El documento
the issues of the lawyer car to go into
las cues estas de el abogado car entrar
depth but the lawyer what he signed
profundidad pero el abogado lo que firmó
in
en
Thai the document This you can
tailandés el documento Este puedes
speak mass here you have the
hablar misa aquí lo tienes la
lawyer's statement and he tells you
declaración del abogado y te lo dice
very clearly he signed With his consent
bien claro firmó Bajo su consentimiento
and nobody did anything to him nobody deceived him and
y nadie le hizo nada nadie le engañó y
everything No, no, we're going to see an appeal
todo No no vamos a ver un recurso
studies the trial and it is presented based on
estudia al juicio y se presenta en base
the trial and in the trial it was
al juicio y en el juicio quedó
proven because no one could contradict
demostrado porque nadie pudo contradecir
because in the end it is only Daniel's word
porque al final es solo la palabra de
against the rest you understand what
Daniel contra el resto me entiendes lo
you have to say if there are they are called the
que ti que decir si hay se llaman los
lawyers and Daniel had the opportunity to
abogados y Daniel tuvo la oportunidad de
ask the lawyer if he had signed
preguntarle al abogado si había firmado
such and such and he answered him and there is the trial you have
tal y y le contestó y está el juicio
his statement here you have all
ties su declaración aquí tienes todas
the statements So if the only thing
las declaraciones Entonces si lo único
you present a a pleading for
que tú presentas un un un un alegato per
a pleading an appeal or an answer
un alegato un recurso o una contestación
an appeal in which it is based solely
un recurso en el cual se basa únicamente
on that Daniel must be believed  that how is it
en que hay que creer a Daniel eso cómo
going to prosper I mean no no no how do
va a prosperar O sea no no no el cómo le
you take away the truth or the
quitas tú la la la la verdad o la
veracity from the lawyer or the police that
veracidad al abogado o a la policía que
here in Spain for example the police
aquí en España por ejemplo la policía
have that little bit of veracity you in a
tiene ese puntito de veracidad tú en una
fine or in anything the
multa o en cualquier cosa la vo de
police voice V more than yours but the thing is that I've
policía V más que la tuya pero es que yo
already seen that every crazy thing in
ya he visto que cada cada locura en
Spain many times man that depending on
España muchas veces tío que dependiendo
who you get they are so guarantors that I'm
quien te toque son tan garantistas que
telling you there are
que ya te digo
some there are some issues
sea hay algun hay algunas cuestiones
here but come on how do you prove that
aquí pero vamos tú cómo demuestras que
Daniel Sancho confessed eh what they put
Daniel Sancho confesó eh lo lo que ponen
in his statement was devised by the police
en su declaración se la ideó la policía
and it was not a confession of his no no no no
y no fue una confesión suya no no no no
but I'm not referring to that I mean I'm
pero no me refiero a eso o sea e me
referring to issues of this document
refiero a cuestiones de este documento
is not valid because it was not there did not have
no es válido porque no estaba no tenía
a good translator in Spanish okay it will
un buen traductor en españ coye por
be they have not put it there translated
estará no se la han puesto ahí traducido
and he signed as if it was fine and he
y firmó como que estaba bien y estaba de
agreed his signature is on the document And
acuerdo está su firma en el documento Y
then why did I say here in the appeal
entonces por qué di aquí en el recurso
that no Of course Why did Miguel say
que no Claro Por qué decía Miguel por
why did Samuel Benítez say that the police hit him
qué decía Samuel Benítez que le pegó la
or that he coerced him no and why
policía o que lo coaccion no y por qué
The cuckoo said for the same reason Miguel
decía el cuco por lo mismo por Miguel
Ricard says that the Civil Guard hit him, they are
ricard dice que le pegó la guardia civil
not telling the truth in things in this
faltan a la verdad en cosas de este
appeal. Of course they are not telling the truth, it is not that they are not telling the
recurso Claro que faltan a la verdad no
truth, they are not telling the
es que falten a la verdad faltan a la
legal truth that is there. Let's see
verdad jurídica que está ahí vamos a ver
if Daniel Sancho is saying I
si Daniel Sancho está diciendo Yo me
signed something that I didn't know what it said,
firmé una cosa que no sabía lo que ponía
why didn't he refuse at the time. Look, there
por qué no se negó en ese momento Mira
is a very simple thing in the appeal, it
hay una cosa muy sencilla en el recurso
says that Daniel Sancho never admitted,
dice que Daniel Sancho nunca admitió
as it is
como viene redactado en la en la en la
written in the
como viene redactado en en en la
statement, the way in which he killed Ewin
declaración la forma en la que mata ewin
Arrieta, and it is exactly the same as how he
Arrieta y es Exactamente igual que como
does it in the video, that is, when the
la hace en vídeo o sea cuando está la
reconstruction of the events is there, he is the one who
reconstrucción de los hechos es el que
goes around saying, I hit him, that's how you hit him. If they have
va diciendo le pegué así le pegas si tú
made a false preparation of you, a
te han hecho una confección falsa una
false confession, and all you have
confesión falsa y tú lo único que has
done is film it, why do you say the same thing
hecho es filmar porque dices lo mismo
when they are recording a video? Let me
cuando están grabando un vídeo me
explain or not, I exp exp, I mean, let's
explico o no me exp exp o sea vamos a
see, this is very easy, I can say one
ver esto es muy fácil yo puedo decir 1
thing, how do I prove it, I mean, how do I
cosas cómo lo demuestro o sea cómo
prove that Ewin Arrieta attacked me?
demuestro que ewin eta me agredió
sexually if the coroner channeled my
sexualmente si el forense canalizó mis
wounds and there is the statement in the
heridas y está la declaración en el
trial that you have here the statement
juicio que la tienes aquí la declaración
is telling you, it is telling you that
te está diciendo te está diciendo que
the wounds the wounds that
las de heridas las heridas que tiene el
Daniel Sancho's body has are wounds from
cuerpo de Daniel Sancho son heridas de
a person who has defended that and
una persona que está ha defendido que y
also gives you a very simple simile they are
además te pone un símil muy sencillo son
the wounds that would have If a person is
las heridas que tendría Si una persona
drowning and tries to save his
se está ahogando e intenta salvar su
life I mean I mean how do you say
vida o sea quiero decir cómo dices tú
that you have been attacked if you don't even have
que has sido agredido si no tienes ni
a wound from aggression he says that he has
una herida de agresión dice que tiene
wounds that are not from violence that
heridas que no son de violencia de que
violence has been used against
se le hay ejercido una violencia hacia
him no that nobody has attacked him in a
él no que no lo ha atacado nadie en una
fight in a fight you have to have ideas
pelea en una pelea tienes que tener idas
you have to have wounds the opponent
tú tiene que tener heridas el oponente
wounds from a fight not wounds that someone else has
heridas de pelea no heridas de que otro
defended then Of course if he
haya defendido entonces Claro si eso te
is telling you that in court and you are going to
lo está diciendo en el juicio y tú vas a
say something else how does he prove it there is
decir otra cosa cómo lo demuestra no hay
nothing that can dem then it is still
nada que lo pueda dem entonces sigue
his word against the forensics
siendo su palabra contra de los forenses
against the police the appeal has
contra de la policía el recurso tiene
three basic keys point one you have to
tres claves básicas punto una hay que
believe Daniel Yes or yes because
creer a Daniel Sí o sí porque lo dice
Daniel says so two Win Arrieta's lawyers
Daniel dos los abogados de Win Arrieta
are scoundrels he says it very clearly
son unos sinvergüenzas lo dice muy claro
in fact the  figure of the lawyer treats her
De hecho la figura del abogado la trata
as if she were the one they were with
como como si fuera con quien estuvieran
exactly and third Well in fact he calls him a scoundrel
exacto y tercero Bueno de hecho le llama
shameless tero throughout
sinvergüenza vergüenza tero durante todo
the entire appeal he calls him Shameless
el recurso lo llama Sinvergüenza
literally throughout the entire appeal
literalmente durante todo el recurso
several times third the
varias veces tercero la policía
Thai police the lawyers of the
tailandesa los abogados del Estado
Thai State because the Thai State puts it
tailandés porque lo pone el estado
on Daniel the translators of the
tailandés a Daniel los traductores del
Thai State are all
Estado tailandés son todos unos
corrupt who have conspired to put
corruptos que han conspirado para meter
Daniel sách in jail and put him in
a Daniel sách la cárcel y que le caiga
prison but that's what that's what
cadena per a eso a lo que a Eso es lo
I'm referring to
que me a eso es lo que yo me refiero
here in Spain eh trials have been annulled
aquí en España eh se han anulado juicios
okay very strong also some that the
vale muy fuertes además alguno que el
judge has made a comment the court
juez ha hecho un comentario el tribunal
has made you know So that's where I
ha hecho sabes Entonces ahí es donde yo
say yes yes things are as
digo si si son las cosas como las está
the appeal is commenting on the issue of the
comentando el recurso el tema de la
Translation I don't know what no no but he does talk But he does
Traducción no sé qué no no pero si habla
talk about the
Pero si habla de el
paper no but not the interrogation I
papel no pero no el interrogatorio me
mean when he is arrested the paper
refiero a cuando él es detenido el papel
that he signs of I don't know what export of I do
que firma de no sé qué de exportación de
n't know how much
no sé cuánto
now of course and you have here in the trial is
ahora claro y tienes aquí en el juicio
that the problem is that yes I can
es que el problema es que sí yo puedo
say many things but during the
decir muchas cosas pero durante el
trial what came out because you take Ah
juicio qué salió porque tú coges a Ah
okay he doesn't tell you what he tells you  is that you
vale no te dice lo que te dice es que
have interpreted more in Thailand
habéis interpretado más en Tailandia
you have misinterpreted what Daniel
habéis interpretado mal lo que Daniel
wanted to say because he is Spanish and you
quería decir porque es español y usted
I am Thai So you have
Soy tailandés Entonces lo hab
interpreted it as leaving racists
interpretado como dejando de racistas
because they are looking down on you for being
porque están menospreciando por serlo
Spanish and such I mean I want to say what is
español y tal O sea quiero decir qué hay
in the appeal because we go with that of the
en el recurso porque vamos con lo del
paper that you were talking about from
papel ese que estabas diciendo de
immigration Daniel says that he signed
inmigración Daniel dice que a él firmó
a paper And such But the thing is that they themselves
un papel Y tal Pero es que ellos mismos
called three immigration police officers
llamaron a tres policías de inmigración
who testified in the trial and Daniel
que declararon en el juicio y Daniel
had the opportunity to ask
tuvo la oportunidad de preguntarle a
those immigration police officers come here
esos policías de inmigración vienes aquí
the testimony of the three police officers and
las testificales de los tres policías y
when Daniel asked them they said it
cuando Daniel le preguntó lo dijeron
very clearly we have not deceived
bien claro nosotros no hemos engañado a
anyone it is a totally
nadie es es un un recurso totalmente
legal resource or in other words we were a person who
legal o sea nosotros era una persona que
was suspected of having done something and by
era sospechosa de haber hecho algo y por
our laws your passport is withdrawn
nuestras leyes se te retira el pasaporte
and you are detained if later during the
y se te retiene si luego durante el
repatriation process of us
proceso de repatriación de que te
expelling you from Thailand it turns out that you
echemos de de Tailandia resulta que
enter as a suspect in a murder
entras como sospechoso de un asesinato
that revocation is dropped until the
cae esa revocación hasta que se resuelva
murder is resolved and that is what happened and
lo del asesinato y eso fue lo que pasó y
the police officers who confessed in
lo dicen los policías que confesaron en
the trial say so of course one thing is that  you go ahead
el juicio claro una cosa es que tú cojas
and make an appeal and say that what
y hagas un recurso y digas que eso que
the police officers confessed was misinterpreted
han confesado esos policías está mal
but that's not what they're doing
interpretado pero es que ellos no hacen
they're not questioning what was
eso ellos no están cuestionando lo que
declared in the trial because they can't
se declaró en el juicio porque no pueden
They're questioning what happened
Ellos están cuestionando lo que pasó
before the trial but the evidence
antes del juicio pero la prueba
presented which is the evidence of the trial
practicada que es la prueba del juicio
That's what they have to question
Esa es la que tienen que cuestionar
because there's already a trial Even the
porque hay un juicio ya Incluso el
summary is worthless There's a trial
sumario no vale para nada Hay un juicio
in which a series of
en el que se han llevado una serie de
clues and evidence have been taken and a
indicios y de pruebas y ha salido una
life sentence has been issued you have to question that that's what
cadena perpetua tenéis que cuestionar
the appeal has to go on it's
eso sobre eso tiene que ir el recurso es
the evidence presented but not the rest doesn't
la prueba practicada pero no ya lo demás
matter and the trial was very clear
da igual y el juicio quedó muy claro
Okay well look if it seems to you Jos I have
Vale pues mira si te parece Jos yo he
noted down the parts that I have seen as most
anotado las partes que yo he visto más
important or that have caught my
importantes o que más me han llamado la
attention the most if you want to Add
atención a mí si tú quieres Añadir
some of the appeal Thursday Friday
alguna del recurso el jueves viernes
Saturday and Sunday and it turns out that
sábado y domingo y resulta que se apunta
the F agency takes credit on Monday as if
el tanto el lunes la agencia F como que
they have given it to him and they start to say that
le han dado ellos y empiezan a decir que
yes that t very strongly this eh I commented on it
si que t muy fuerte esto eh lo comenté
Oh in my live very strongly the
Ay en mi directo muy fuerte la revista
reading magazine for example and some of course they have
lectura por ejemplo y alguna claro han
taken the information from your  direct and they
cogido la información de tus directos y
quote you as it should be but the F has
te citan como debe ser pero la F ha
taken the Well he has given it as an
cogido la Bueno le ha dado como una
exclusive of his no yes yes yes but not before
exclusiva suya no sí sí sí pero no antes
no they released it on Monday or Tuesday
no ellos lo sacaron el lunes o el martes
and I released it specifically the first
y yo lo saqué concretamente la el primer
headline of F which is that the wide ones
titular de F que es que la los anchos
ask for the trial to be repeated I released it
piden que se repita el juicio lo saqué
on Thursday or Thursday I already said it
yo el jueves o sea el jueves ya lo dije
and they released it on Monday or
yo y ellos lo sacaron el lunes o el
Tuesday well they don't like it Ah I don't care it
martes bueno no les cae bien Ah a mí me
gives me ig a problem they can't like me
da igual a me da ig un problema no le
Look I have divided eh
puedo caer bien Mira yo he dividido eh
the points into premeditation not what they
los puntos en premeditación no lo que
allege about premeditation and what they
alegan sobre la premeditación e lo que
allege about the relationship they had the
alegan sobre la relación que tenían el
issue of money if they are homosexual or not
tema del dinero si son homosexuales o no
okay that they dedicate a few pages to it
vale que le dedican unas cuantas páginas
and the issue of the death penalty okay
y el tema de la pena de muerte vale que
why should it be the most serious penalty or
por qué debería ser la pena más grave o
not the issue of annulling the trial okay and
no el tema de anular el juicio vale y
then the civil part and the crime of
luego la parte civil y el delito de
disappearing documentation let's
desaparecer documentación vamos a
comment on something then on the issue of
comentar algo entonces sobre el tema de
premeditation What is the most eh well
la premeditación Qué es lo más Eh bueno
the juice not of the trial no let's see the
el jugo no de del juicio no a ver los
points that they allege m that a person period the
puntos que alegan m que una persona
we analyze or what we do that yes yes yes if
punto los analizamos o qué hacemos eso
you yes you what I have
sí sí sí si tú si tú lo que yo he
considered that has caught my
considerado que me han llamado la
attention okay if you for whatever reason
atención vale si tú por lo que seas
want to add some more but let's go more
quiere Añadir alguno más pero vamos más
or less it's a little bit of what we have
o menos es un poco lo que lo que hemos
been chewing over during these years
venido masticando durante estos años
okay em alleges that if a person eh
vale em alega que si una persona eh
wants to commit a crime of this caliber
quiere cometer un delito de este Calibre
a Spanish person then it doesn't make
una persona española pues no tiene
any sense that he would go and commit it
ningún sentido que se vaya a cometerlo
being he from Spain and eh and his victim not
siendo él de España y eh y su víctima no
from Latin America that he would go and commit it
de América Latina que se vaya cometerlo
in a country like Thailand that apart from the fact that they do
a un país como Tailandia que aparte de
n't know the place well it is a
que no lo conocen el sitio pues es un
place that has the death penalty Okay
sitio que tiene pena de muerte Vale
then starting from that basis the
entonces partiendo de esa base los
only ones who commit
únicos que cometen asesinatos
premeditated murders are foreigners not to
premeditados son los los foráneos no sea
say that in Spain they only
qui decir que en España solamente
commit premeditated murders people
cometen asesinatos premeditados la gente
who are from Spain are never going to come a
que es de España nunca va a venir un
Pole a Russian an Englishman a German to
polaco un Ruso un inglés un alemán a
commit a murder because since they are from somewhere
cometer un asesinato porque como es de
else it doesn't make sense for them to come
otro lado no tiene sentido que venga
Look, recently a girl
Mira hace poco desapareció una chica que
named Ana María Nevis disappeared she was
se llamaba Ana María nevis que era
American this girl lived in the United
americana esta chica vivía en Estados
States with an uncle er they were rich they
Unidos con un tío er eran de dinero
had a very good company and such and she
tenían una empresa muy buena tal Y
arrived she was from  Colombian but she
llegado ella era origen colombiano pero
lived in in fact her name is María enao What
vivía en de hecho se llama María enao Lo
happens is that she is María vi enao because they
que pasa que es María vi enao porque
take the last name this girl was
cogen el apellido esta muchacha estaba
married I think he was I think eh I don't
casado creo que él era creo eh No me
remember exactly the nationality but I
acuerdo exactamente la nacionalidad pero
think he was from Slovenia or Poland I don't
creo que él era de eslovenia o polaco no
remember a country from there in the
me acuerdo de un país de de allí del
east no well Well it turns out that she is in the
este no bueno Pues resulta que está en
United States they separate her husband
Estados Unidos se separan el marido
wanted the company to be divided 70
quería que la empresa se divid diese 70
30 meaning that she would take 30 70 and
30 o sea que ella se llevase 30 el 70 y
she no longer agreed so they don't
ella ya no estaba de acuerdo tal que no
get along things aren't going very well and she moves
se lleva no iba muy bien y ella se muda
to Spain she comes to live here in Spain
A España se viene a vivir aquí a España
to a to a central part of Madrid
a a un a una parte céntrica de de Madrid
buo Well the husband leaves the country by plane
buo Pues el marido se va país en avión
from the United States he rents a car
desde Estados Unidos alquila un coche
with tinted windows he changes the
con los cristales tintados Le cambia las
license plates he has to Spain and he kills her He kills her It
matrículas tiene a España y la mata la
is assumed because the leather has not appeared
Mata Se supone porque no ha aparecido el
why did he do it like that because he didn't
cuero por qué lo ha hecho así porque no
kill her in the United States that he lives in the
la mató en Estados Unidos que vive en
United States Well because he killed her here in Spain because the whole opportunity presented itself here in Spain I mean the excuse of Why can't that Spaniard commit a premeditated murder in
puede hacer un asesinato premeditado en
Thailand is absurd he thought and I'm going to
Tailandia es absurdo él pensó y te voy a
tell you why he thought of Cangan Island he
decir por qué pensó en la isla de cangan
thought of Cangan Island for several
é pensó en la isla de cangan por varios
reasons the main reason was the date he
motivos el principal motivo era la fecha
chose to commit the August 3rd
que coge para cometer el de agosto el 3
Sorry between the two and the three
de agosto Perdón entre el dos y el tres
what happens in Cangan is that there is the
qué es lo que pasa en cangan que está la
full moon party the
fiesta de la luna llena la fiesta de la
full moon party which is a party in which
luna llena que es una fiesta en la que
almost everyone there are
casi todo el mundo que hay allí son
European tourists therefore a
turistas europeos por lo tanto un tío
European surfer guy is going to go unnoticed
europeo surfero va a pasar desapercibido
yes or yes because they are all the same put
sí o sí porque son todos iguales poned
any video if you want of Cangan
cualquier vídeo si queréis de cangan
Full Moon Party you can search for it
fiesta de la luna llena lo podéis buscar
and you will see on Hat Ring beach which
y Vais a ver en la playa de hat ring que
is where it is celebrated how all are like
es donde se celebra como todos son del
Daniel Sancho guys with caps
perfil de Daniel Sancho tíos con gorras
without shirts with abs in
sin camiseta con abdominales con las
Bermuda shorts kids with long
bermudas chavales con los pelos largos
blond hair I mean you can put it
rubios o sea ponerlo podis ponerlo
because even many people said that
porque incluso mucha gente dicho ese
Daniel No that that Daniel No that because the thing is that they are
Daniel No ese ese Daniel No ese porque
all the same I mean he chose the
es que son todos iguales o sea eligió el
perfect place at the perfect time
sitio perfecto en el momento perfecto
that on the one hand then it is an island that on
eso por un lado luego es una isla que en
that date is overflowing with tourism  that qu
esa fecha está desbordada de turismo eso
What causes the police not to give
qu Qué produce que la policía no de
Abastos does not give Abastos it's like if you are going to
Abastos no da Abastos es como si tú vas
commit something here in Seville you do it
a cometer algo aquí en Sevilla lo haces
during the fair or you do it during Holy Week
en feria o lo haces en semana santa Por
Why Because it's when the city is most
qué Porque es cuando la ciudad está más
crowded just like if you do it during
llena de gente igual que si lo haces en
the Sanfermines they do it during the
en los sanfermines lo hacen los
Sanfermines because that's when there are more people
sanfermines porque es cuando más gente
and the police let's say that they pay
hay y la policía digamos que que presta
less attention than if it were a time when
menos atención que si fuese una fecha en
Things are quiet no Of course
la que La cosa está tranquila no Claro
what he thought Daniel is not stupid Well he
él qué pensaba Daniel no es tonto Bueno
's not stupid Let's see he's not very stupid Daniel
no es tonto A ver no es muy tonto Daniel
thought and would say [ __ ] disappears
pensaba y diría [__] desaparece
during harring sorry the jí during the
durante harring perdón el jí durante la
full moon the full full full Party whatever it
luna llena la full full full Party como
's called disappears during the
se llame desaparece durante la fiesta de
full moon party I file a report or a report is filed
la luna llena yo doy parte o se da parte
or he disappears and it's a guy who has
o desaparece y es un tío que ha
disappeared when the party is over they will look for him they will
desaparecido ya cuando acabe la ya lo
look for him And if he appears
buscarán ya lo buscarán Y si aparece
well and if he doesn't appear also well I mean he will
bien y si no aparece tamb bien o sea
say that we have not eaten a ca that we
dira que no hemos comido una ca que
were partying or for a
estábamos de fiesta o por un momento
given moment I have stopped seeing it clearly What happens that he what he did
dado lo he dejado de ver claro Qué pasa
n't count on was that the
que é con lo que no contaba era con que
parts of the  body in
iban a aparecer las partes del cuerpo en
the landfill that's what it is and the
el vertedero que eso es lo que a y las
parts do not appear in the landfill it would not have been
partes no aparecen en el vertedero no le
necessary to ewin Arrieta
hubiera hechado falta a ewin Arrieta
would have gone would have said Hey look I
hubiera ido hubiera dicho Oye mira que
was with a friend of mine last night at the
estuve con un amigo mío esta noche en la
beach that I did the VAT for the
playa que te he hecho el IVA para la
Fando when he stopped at the police station and he was going to
fando cuando paró en la comisaría é iba
the party and he would have told the
para la fiesta é hubiera dicho a la
police look Sorry it's that I am what he
poliía mira Perdona es que yo est lo que
told him that he was with a friend of mine that
le dijo que estaba con un amigo mío que
V was at a party and such and the police
V estar una fiesta y tal y la policía
would have said okay Don't worry because we
hubiera dicho buena No te preocupes pues
put it here we look for it is what they would have
lo ponemos aquí buscamos es lo que lo
said the same as if you go
hubieran dicho igual que si tú vas ahora
to the police now you are going with a friend
a la policía aú tú te vas con un colega
tonight or rather Easter The
esta noche o sea Semana Santa El
problem is that the body parts appear
problema es que aparecen las partes del
and it coincides with the fact that there is already a
cuerpo y coincide con que ya hay una
report from the sister the sister no the
denuncia de la hermana la hermana no la
sister called ask where the
hermana llamó preguntar Dónde estaba el
brother was he was worried
hermano estaba preocupado
about the body already the sister calls how
her el cuerpo ya la hermana llama como
can a lot of people call okay Well yes well we
puede llamar mucha gente vale Bueno sí
write it down here and the fact is that there are no
pues lo anotamos aquí y es que no hay
more There are no pairs of bodies you understand
más No hay pares de cuerpo me entiendes
what I'm saying there is nothing it coincided
lo que te digo no hay nadaa coincidió
with the fact that the sister was in contact
con que la hermana estaba en contacto
with and  the police report on
con y la denuncia de la policía de
Daniel the three things matched If they do
Daniel se coincidieron las tres cosas Si
n't appear the if the body parts don't appear
no aparecen la si no aparecen las partes
both what the
del cuerpo tanto lo que esta hablando la
sister is saying and the report that Daniel makes
hermana como la denuncia que pone Daniel
very simple t suppose that you have a
muy sencillo t ponte que tú tienes un
friend of gal and he says Hey Javi that I'm going to
amigo de gal y te dice Oye Javi que voy
go on Holy Wednesday to spend
a ir el miércoles Santo a pasar contigo
Holy Thursday with you you know like
el jueves Santo tú sabes como el jueves
Holy Thursday in Seville the early hours of
Santo en Sevilla la madrugada del jueves
Holy Thursday and the guy goes on Holy Thursday you
Santo y el tío coge el jueves Santo tú
go and go to the National Police
coges y te vas a la Policía Nacional la
this kid's sister calls you in
hermana de este chaval te llama a ti por
the morning Hey Javi Do you know anything about my
la mañana Oye Javi Tú sabes algo de mi
brother is that he went with you Look,
hermano que es que se fue contigo Mira
no, I was with him last night and we
yo no yo estuve con él anoche y nos
got into a row and I stopped seeing him and
metimos en una bulla y lo dejé de ver y
until today Hey go to the police and you
hasta hoy Oye llégate a la policía y tú
go to the police you say that I
te llegas a la policía dice usted que yo
was with a friend of mine last night in the
estuve anoche con un colega mío en la
early hours watching La Macarena and that he
madrugada viendo La Macarena y que nos
distracted us and the Sister says that
despista y la Hermana dice que no
the police haven't shown up what are you going to tell me
aparece la policía qué te va a decir
Okay then tell me his name his date they're not going to
Bueno pues dime su nombre su dat no van
comb the streets what he was dressed and
a a peinar las calle cómo iba vestido y
then we'll wait  24 hours 48 hours and I
ya vamos a esperar 24 horas 48 horas y
looked for him And that has happened the
lo busc Y eso lo hua pasado la
difference is if you go and by chance in
diferencia es si tú vas y casualmente en
a verton pieces of your friend have appeared
un verton ha aparecido Trozos de tu
the thing does not seem different to
amigo la cosa no da pinta diferente a
see a point here I am going to give him I do not I
ver un punto aquí le le voy a dar yo no
mean a point is an idiot to go
O sea un punto es gilipolla para irte a
commit a type of crime like that to a place
cometer un tipo de delito así a un sitio
where there is the death penalty idiot it was
donde hay pena de muerte gilipo ya fue
no You think he knew that there was the
no Tú crees que sabía que había pena de
death penalty I think he did not know let's see in
muerte yo creo que no lo sabía a ver de
all way I did not think that they were going to catch him it
to forma no pensaba que lo iban a [__]
is that I do not think IB was going to catch the
es que tampoco piens pens que IB a [__]
same as that is what people think and also
igual que eso la gente piensa y además
this you can see the statistics that because there are
esto lo podéis ver las estadísticas que
higher penalties there are fewer
Al haber penas más altas hay menos
crimes that is false it is proven that
delitos eso es falso está demostrado que
because there are higher penalties there are fewer
no por haber penas más altas hay menos
crimes in the United States where the
delitos en Estados Unidos que está la
death penalty exists in many states it is one of the
pena de muerte en muchos estados es de
countries with the most murders and
los países que más asesinatos hay y
serial murders in Japan the
asesinatos en serie en Japón existe la
death penalty exists in Asian countries
pena de muerte en países asiáticos
a lot I mean it is not proven that
montones O sea no está demostrado que no
because the death penalty exists people
por existir la pena de muerte la gente
commit less And statistically you
comete menos Y eso estadísticamente lo
can look at that of course he thinks that they are not
podéis mirar claro él piensa que no lo
going to catch him  and and he doesn't think about the in the
van a [__] y y no piensa en la en la
penalty he's not valuing the penalty here in
pena no está valorando la pena aquí en
Spain it would have been I'm
España hubiera sido ya te
telling you Oh
digo Oh